Ek Rekha is fasting, don't go anywhere,
keep watching the news 2018 From Gurjar social worker
Saiya Agra, heartiest wishes for a
better Republic Day to all the district residents and the countrymen. From
Rocky Yadav, junior engineer, Saiya Agra,
heartiest wishes for Republic Day to all the district residents and the countrymen. From
Sanjay Traders distributor Munshi
Panna Masala Udyog Pvt Ltd Agra
's Nitesh Agarwal and Sanjay Goyal,
heartiest wishes and congratulations for Republic Day to all the countrymen and the state residents. From
Yoga Youth Brigade Uttar Pradesh Ajay
Tomar, state president Dr Dharmendra Chaudhary,
president Ramratan Tomar, state treasurer
Virendra Rajput, district security chief,
heartiest wishes and congratulations for Republic Day to all the countrymen and the Agra residents. From
Pathak Borewell Drilling Contact Water
Supply & Road Roller, address near petrol pump,
Bhind Road, Gole Ka Mandir, Gwalior,
Madhya Pradesh's proprietor Monu Pathak,
heartiest wishes for a better Republic Day to all the countrymen. To
contact mobile number 98 2767
5146 926  Contact on 373 10898 2 years 452 323 34
When I, Kishore Kumar Badhana, Executive
Officer, Nagar Palika Parishad, Khoda Makanpur,
District Ghaziabad,
send my heartiest greetings on the 72nd Republic Day, along with this,
I appeal to the residents of my area, city
and state that
as you all know that
our country India is in the grip of the global pandemic of Corona
and the one that has
gone straight away is a thing of good news, but even
after this, we have to take precautions, two
yards distance is necessary, along with this,
timing has to be done by hand in the office,
apart from this, there are two vaccinations, that vaccination will be
100% for everyone, this is the
commitment of our Prime Minister and in this, the
rate protocol has been decided that first
our frontline warriors will be given the
professional vaccine,
after that, the elderly above 50 years of age will be
given the vaccine and after that, those who are
already affected by Corona and
work in such areas where there is a
greater possibility of Corona, then those people should be given
this vaccine.  If it comes, wait for it patiently.
Similar rumours are being
spread by people
saying all sorts of things and are coming to you secretly through social media. There is
no truth in such rumours. The
words spoken by the Prime Minister are
proof in themselves that this is a 100%
safe vaccine and it will definitely be
beneficial for you. Do not forget that
even after the vaccine, you will have to follow the principle of two yards distance and
mask is necessary.
With this, I
send my heartiest greetings on Republic Day.
Jai Hind, Jai Bharat. On
behalf of Nagar Palika Parishad Khoda Makanpur Ghaziabad,
heartiest greetings on Republic Day to all the countrymen.
Nagar Palika Parishad Khoda Makanpur
Ghaziabad appeals to all the residents of the district to
keep the following things in mind for the betterment of the city and
to prevent virus infection, wear a mask compulsorily
and
wash hands with soap for 40 seconds at regular intervals and
maintain a distance of two yards in your daily routine.
Do not leave your house unless it is very necessary, do not allow
any kind of crowd to
form nor be a part of it. Nirukt
Telemedicine  For medical treatment,
download Ghaziabad Delhi Treatment App from Google Play Store In Swachhta Survey
2021, citizens are appealed to
cooperate with the municipality to make their city number one in the cleanliness ranking Never use
all products made of plastic and both spoons, plates and word
disposal properly and paper
bags Do not keep
building material waste on the
roadside If
any material waste is found
kept on the roadside during surprise inspection, a fine of Rs
50,000 will be imposed as per the instructions of National Green Tribunal, New Delhi
Before constructing a building, submit the building map and
documents as witnesses to the municipality Get the
registration of births and deaths done
within the stipulated time limit of 31 days
Cooperate and guide the municipality in development works Do
not encroach on government property Cooperate with the municipality in
identifying encroachers, illegal occupants and land mafias
and submit their name and address along with
proof in a sealed envelope to the municipality
office Your identity will be kept secret
Tell me more